The shoot is not happening on the shelf.
Were you hit by a four wheeler
from behind or from the front or did someone else hit you like this,
tomorrow I come and this gets rejected etc.  So
brother, you stay there, I
swear on my mother that I will destroy you like this.  [Music]
So guys welcome back to the channel and my
car was in an accident this Sunday.
Ok?  So what is it that I
mean in this video today, why is this video special for you
?  First thing is first let me
show you what the damage is like.
Like you will get to know the build quality etc.
So my speed would have been somewhere between 60 and 70
[nasal sound].
Look, all this has happened in this.  It is
broken from here.  The meter is going.   The
handle is completely crooked.  These headlights
etc. have gone from here.  Ok?
[sound of clearing throat] It's broken here
and this whole lady's
footrest here is gone too.  This
entire gear system is over.
Look, it is happening like this.  This is how it is happening.
Ok?  This has happened.  It has been rubbed from here.
Ok?  This is what happened to the engine, it is worn out.
So what it means is that it is okay
considering the speed at which the accident happened.
Build quality.  People say
that this and that meaning is correct, friend.  Ok.
Look, let's try this now
because after that I got a slight injury in my leg.
Ok?  So
because of this here because I have
already had a bump at the time of the accident.
I'll show you what happened.  Look,
this means what is speed?
How did I actually have the accident?  I was moving at speed.
Then suddenly a
stone came surprisingly.  There was a big stone there, so
what happened while applying the brakes?  The car hit that
[nasal sound] stone
and it flew into the air.   It was a
big stone.  This accident happened in my Chilla.
Brother, look, there is something like this.  I ca
n't see the meter, friend.  Gives cells.  Okay,
how about it.   It is
not starting.  Let's check it
out.  [nasal sound] Let's move
it back a little.  Look at this handle.
Oh, the system is becoming terrible, friend.
So
first let me stand it properly.
Then I start and then I show you.
Ok?
So brother, let's first try to start it, but it is
not happening,
once again the
air comes, why are you running it forcefully, you are
not running it, you have to take it, you should not put it in the flame, mother,
this is also blocked.  What is happening,
friend?  Brother, car means there are some
things in it, it
troubles my mind a lot, I swear to God,
how much will it cost to buy a car, tell me overall,
this is some system, we will see the rest, friend, this is a
car.
Ok?  Now let's see how it goes.
What all remains.  I have GD insurance for
this.  Ok?  So I will check that out as well and let
you know how it will be.
Whether any problem etc. arises or
not.  For now, let's take him along.
So brother, in this video I
wanted to show each and every thing properly as to
how the insurance claim etc. is done
or how it is not done.  What problems do
I face?  But let me tell you one thing
that the insurance with go digit go digits is
not better than IDFC,
I felt this way because my friend had an
accident, his insurance was with IDFC, he was with
ICICI Lambd, so
if I had heard his call recording or the
call that came in front of me, then the person was asking in a
genuine manner that
brother tell me how it happened, how it happened
and these good digit ones, that is, they were
straight forward in everything that you were hit by a four wheeler
from behind or from the front or like this, I
mean, they hit you or someone else, I said
brother, nothing like that happened to me, I had no idea about any four wheeler
or anyone else,
I was coming, a stone came from the front and the car hit it,
due to imbalance the car went
down, I fell on the road, I
told them like this, they were okay, still they were
asking like this in between, on top of that
they made me call as if they had
called, after that they said that I am
calling from this, this, that  So what happened is now
every time we go for a Sunday ride, so
in the middle of work his call came and I
mistakenly said that brother it was Sunday, I mean
he asked when did the accident happen, I said
first I said Saturday then he said no
we said it was right on Sunday but that day I had gone on
Saturday so I had gone to the temple, I
mean I had gone on Saturday, all this happened, so
now I feel that
he might have brought this thing negative
because I then asked the showroom guy, I
said friend, then after some time as soon as I
disconnected the call, after two-four minutes when I was
free from work, I
realized that brother I probably said it wrong
because I had said 28th in it
because my accident actually happened on
Saturday, on 28th I
mistakenly told him it was Sunday i.e. 29th, so on
his [nasal voice] behalf
I then asked the showroom guy,
I said brother such a thing is such a thing,
what can be done about this?  He has said that there are
chances that it may get rejected.  Rest,
he will come tomorrow, do one thing, give him his
number.  Then I arranged his number etc.
personally
because the number from which the call comes is toll
free.  So that call etc. does
not get connected.  Ok?  When I arranged that guy's
number, I called him.
But after that I told him that brother, it was like this.
I was busy at work.  I
told you this by mistake.  I immediately
decided that this whole process of
taking the number etc. and asking them whether it was cancelled
or it would be done, it would not be possible.  There will be approval or
not.  My claim, this entire
process was completed within 5 minutes.
I immediately called him and told him
that sir, such and such is the matter.  After that the
guy said, okay I will come and check it tomorrow.
If he comes tomorrow, then he will come tomorrow, obviously he will
come,
but if he comes tomorrow and rejects me like this, then
brother, you stay put, I will destroy you like this,
I swear on my mother,
brother, if you call any person, I will give you the
recording of everything
etc., then he will not even say properly
that brother, this thing can happen, although I was
also going to say that you can call me when you are free, that is, we can
talk later,
because I am actually on duty,
so I will not be able to focus that much, so at that
time there were many things, there were customers etc.,
I had to handle them too, that is why
this thing happened.  Ok?  Now come and
subscribe to the channel.
What remains?  If the
Go Digit Go Digit people do not make my claim, then
what procedures do I have to follow?
How to complain about that?  What should be done?
What can a common man do on his own
?  Because brother, I cannot invest Rs
25-26,000 from my pocket.  Whereas
I have an insurance for that vehicle.
Why would I apply it?  However, if it is in lieu of a date, then
I
said Sunday instead of Saturday.  If they take that thing with them
and their calls, I mean brother, you were
treating it in such a way that who hit
you, hit you from the left,
hit you from the right, did a four wheeler do a tool, hey, what is this
thing of hit, I myself am saying
that I had an accident, I got
unbalanced, the car hit a stone due to which the
car
went down and this happened to the car there,
so I told him
everything in a proper manner, this is what happened to me about one other thing, let's
see what happens, should we cancel it or
not, though there are chances that it will get
cancelled but I still told him
immediately as soon as I got some free time,
now let's see what happens.  Ok?  Please
subscribe to the channel.  I will continue the rest of this video.
I will put every single thing else in the shorts.  I had also
made a video of the claim etc., I will upload that also
in the ss.  Keep checking that now.
Ok?  Please subscribe and
keep watching the rest of the videos.
[Music]